Guide to the Meyer Lissner Papers, 1903-1923 (inclusive), 1910-1920 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- AS - AV
  - L.A. Playground Dept. - 1912, 13& Bd. of Playground Commis.; Bessie D. Stafford, Pres.; s. Charles S. Lamb, Sec.
  - L.A. Police Dept. - 1912, 17st. s. C.E. Sebastian, chief; s. McClain & Denman; offrs., st. C.E. McKeag, sec. Bd. Police Commrs.; st. J.L. Butler, chief
  - L.A. Polytechnic H. S. Commerce Club 1915
  - L.A. Power Bond Com. - 1914
  - L.A. Public Utilities Bd. - 1911, 12, 14, 15, n.d.s. Theo. B. Comsteck engr. & sec (Lissner = pres.) t. ? Charles E. Warner, t. Thomas Foulkes, pres.
  - L.A. Public Works Bd. - 1906, 12, 13, n.d.s. Horace B. Ferris, s s. M.M. Humphreys, cmmr.
  - L.A. Shipbuilding & Dey Dock Co. - 1919
    - s. F.G. Phillipps, comptroller; F.P. Duncklee, asst. sec.
    - s. P.H. Barratt, sec to L.V. Hedrick Comptroller; Etle M. Leaf, v. pres.
    - s. Harry C. Todd, sec to E.M. Leaf
  - L.A. Sec. of Social Hygiene - 1912s. Mrs. Bertholt Baruch, fin. sec.
  - L.A. Tax & License Collector - 1912t. Clarence M. Taggert
  - L.A. Y.M.C.A. - 1907, 11, 12, 13, 18, 20s. D.E. Luther, gen. sec. asst. sec. exten fund sec.
    - s. George Ballmann, exten. sec.; C.F. Quillian, asst. gen. sec.
    - s. R.E. Blewett, fin. sec.
  - L.A. (City) Civil Service - 1911s. W.A. Spalding
  - L.A. Convention League - L.A. 1911s. Frank Wiggins, sec.
  - Los Angeles County Assessor - 1911s. L.O. Weed, chf. deputy to Ed. W. Hepk
  - L.A. Co. Civil Service Cmm. - 1913, 15-17, 20st. & s. F.E. Doty, sec.
  - L.A. Co. District Atty. - 1920(Thomas Lee Woolwine) s. Tracy C. Becker
  - L.A. Co. Registrar of Voters - 1917ptd. D.B. Lyons
  - L.A. Co. Republican Central Com. - 1908, 12, 20, 21s. Bradner W. Lee, chrmm Fred Frank
    - s. Dell A. Schweitzer, Sec.; Russ Avery, chairman.; Claire Woolwine spkos B
    - st. Louis M. Dole, chairman State Com.; Alfred L. Bartlett chairman. Co. Com
  - Lubin, Simon J. - Sacramento 1915, 18cmmr & pres. Calif Immigration & Housing Cmm. of Wenstock, Lubun & Co.
  - Lucas, William Palmer - S.F. 1915prof. Pediatrics U.C. Med. Schi
  - Lundeen, K. & Co. - L.A. 1916s. Wm. Penn Henley
  - Luther, D.E. - 29A, 1908, 11gen. Sec. L.A. Y.M.C.A.
  - Lyman, E.D. - L.A. 1917atty
  - Lyon, Henry, H. L.A., Sacramento 1913, 16, 17Calif. Senate Com. Labert Capital
  - Lyon Fireproof Storage Co. - W.A. 1918s. Frank L. Allen, Sec
  - Luce, Edgar A. - San Diego 1907, 08-13, 15-18, 20, 21atty sec. San Diego Co. L-R Repub. Club, candidate for D.A., member campanger com. Roosevelt Progressive Repub Cl. of San Diego Calif. Senate, 2nd Lt. A.S.S.C. at U. of Cincinnate, superior Cf. Judge
  - Lyons, D.B. - L.A. 1908, 11, 13, 16, 18, 20, 21Lyons Dividends Co., pres. & mgr. Public School Com. of One Hundred, chomn., L.A. Co. Registrar of Voters
  - Lyons, Harry - Sacremento 1917Calif Assb.
  - McAleer, Thomas - L.A. 1915L.A. Co. Registrar of Voters
  - MacArthur, Walter - S.F. 1918U.S. Shipping Cmmrs off. - Navig. Service Dept. Commerce
  - McAtee, Sylvester S. - S.F. 1914,14sec. Johnson-Eshleman Non-Partisan Club, sec. Repub. St. Central Cem.
  - McBean, J. T. - L.A. 1912,13sec. Calif Assn. of Investment Corporations
  - MacBeth, Hugh E. - L.A. 1918, 26atty ? Colored Johnson for Pres. Club
  - ? McBride, J. H. - Pasaslena 1915,17,18M.D., Calif Immigration & Housing Comm.
  - McBryde, Warren H. - Pinole 1912, S.F. 1919chrmn Contra Costa Co Repub. Cent. Com.
  - McCallum, John H. - S. F. 1920pres. Calif. St. Harbor Commrs., (1)
  - McCan, Mrs. David C. - L.A. 1910,13Political Equality League pres. Friday Morning Club
  - McClure, W. F. - Sacramento 1915,16,17California Engineering Dep State engr.
  - McConnell, W. L. - L.A. 1913Indus. Acc. Bd. Ins. Mgr. L.A. Dist.
  - McCormick, Mrs. Medill - Chicago 1912
  - McCormick, Paul J. - L.A. 1912,18judge Superior Ct.
  - McCowan, Barclay - Bakersfield, Cal. 1912mgr. owner edison Rand
  - McCabe, Alexander - Sacramento 1911 - 1920pvt. see to Gov. Johnson, Calif. Ins. Cmm.
  - McClatchy, Charles K. - Sacramento 1910, 1919, 20editor, Sacramento Bee
  - McCormick, Medill - Wa. D.C., Chicago 1912-15,17,19U.S. Rep from Ill. Ill. House of Reps. National Roosevelt Committee
  - McDonald, C.C. - Austin, Tex. 1912Texas. See of St.
  - McDonald, Hewey M. - L.A. 1908pres. L. A. Bond & Mortgage Co.
  - McDuffie, Duncan - Berkeley 1913pres. Berkeley City Planning Com.
  - McFarland, John C. - Sacramento 1917exec. sec. to Gov. Step
  - McFarlane, Peter Clark - N.Y. 1912author
  - McIlhenny, John A. - Washington, D.C. n.d.form letter pres U.S. Civ. Setv. Cmm.
  - McKeen, B.W. - Kingsburg, Cal. 1915ed. & prep. Kingsburg Recorder
  - MacKeigan, Alexander - L.A. 1913-15Joint Bur. of Appraisal
  - McKenzie, Charles, - L.A. 1910,11,13L.A. City Council
  - McKinney, J. G. - L.A. 1906,07,11,12mgr. L.A. Ice & Cold Storage Co.
  - McKnight, James S. - L.A. 1916
  - McLachlan, James - Washington, D.C. 1909,11U.S. Rep.
  - McLeod, George E. - S.F. 1916spl. agt. Calif Water Cmm.
  - McLucas, Victor R. - Santa Monica 1921City Atty.
  - McMillan, J. - L.A. 1921Calif & Mex. SS Co., Swayne & Hoyt, Inc
  - McMurray, Orrin K. - Berkeley 1919U.C. School of Jurisprudence
  - McNab, James - S.F. 1910 -chrmn Calif Leges. Com. Panama-Pacific Internal
  - McQuillin, Eugene - St. Louis, Missouri 1914Missouri Circuit Ct. judge
  - McVay, W.E. - L.A. 1910-13v.p. German Amer. Savings Bank
  - McVicar, John - Des Moines, Iowa 1916,11supt. Dept. of Sts. & Pub. Imp.
  - Mabury, P.R. - L.A. 1908,11
  - Mackrille, William R. - S.F. 1910,11chief dep. clerk Calif Supreme Ct.
  - Magnes, I.D. - N.Y. 1917,18,&19res buyer
  - Mallory, L.B. - S.F. 1918? Indus Acc. Com.
  - Maltbie, Mike R. - N.Y. 1912Ommr. N.Y. Pub Service Comm.
  - Manchester, May W. - Santa Barbara 1912asst. see Sta. B. Co. Rep. Prog. Co. Central Com.
  - Manning, C. D. - L.A. 1910L.A. Co. Bd. of Supervisors
  - Madsen, Martin C. - S.F., Sacramento 1912, 15-20? Roosevelt Progressive Repub. Lg., pvt. sec., to W. D. Stephens
  - Marcheank, George - Madera 1912Madera Co. Herticultural Cmmt.
  - Marin Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - San Raphael 1912s. S. M. Augustine exec. comm.; s. Robert E. Graham - Marin C. Clerk
  - Marshall, George H. - Long Beach 1912 -pres. Roosevelt Club.
  - Marshall, R. B. - Wn. D.C. 1911Interior Dept., U.S. Geol. Survey, chf. geograp
  - Marston, George W. - San Diego 1907
  - Martin, Irving - Stockton 1907, 08, 15, 18, 19Record Publishing Co. see Lg. of L-R Repub. Cls. of Calif., Stockton Record, pres. Calif. Water Comm.
  - Martin, Norman R. - L.A. 1916, 17supt. L.A. Co. Dept. of Charities
  - Maryland Hotel Co. - Pasadena 1909, 13, 14s. D.M. Linnard, mgr. (Maryland H., Pasadena; Virginia H., Long Beach Huntington, Pasaolena
  - Mass, Highway Cmm. - Beston 1912s. Frank I. Bieler, see.
  - Mass, Savings Ins. League - Boston, 1914s. Alice H. Grady, fin. sec.
  - Mather, Stephen T. - Chicago 1911, 12
  - Mathews, H. D. - San Jose, Cal. 1907mayor
  - Mathews, W. B. - L.A. 1918atty.
  - Matthews, J. L. - Covina 1910editor, Covina Argus
  - Matthewson, Walter G. - San Jose 1918Calif. Indus. Welfare Comm.
  - Maxwell, George H. - Washington, D.C. 1920exec. dir. Nat'l Reclamation Assoc.
  - Mayer, Ernest - Chicago 1920
  - Medaris, Wm. R. - Chicago 1912acting see. Progr. Natl Com.
  - Mehagian, Avak S. - Pasadena 1920Jewish campaign work Palestine, Syria
  - Meeker, Royal - Wn., D.C. 1917Cmmt. Labor Statistics: Labor Dep.
  - Melbourne, J. A. - N. Y. 1912s Nat'l Republican Alliance
  - Mendenhall, W. C. - Wn. D.C., 1911Dept. of Interior, U.S. Geol Survey, chief Land Classification Bd.
  - Mendocino Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - 1910, 12s. H.F. Milliken, chrmn; Ft. Breg s. W.O. White, sec. Ukiah - owner & ed., Ukiah Republican Press
  - Merced Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - Stevinson 1911, 12t. W. H. Joy, see. s. W. E. Morton,, chrmn., L. R. Johnson, Co. Auditor
  - Merchants & Manufacturers Assn. - S. F. 1914t Seneca C. Beach, sec., mgr.; s. H. H. Hastings (Oakland)
  - Merriam, C. E. - Chicago 1908, 09, 12, 13u. of Chicago, Poli Sci Dept.
  - Meyer, B. H. - (Chicago Wn. D.C.) 1911fr. Wisconsin
  - Meyer, H. A. - Wn. D. C. 1911confidential sec. to Sec. of Interior
  - *Meyer, Martin A. - S. F. 1911, 13rabbi, Temple Emanu-el Visalia
  - Middlecoff, W. W. - L. A. 1915, 19atty
  - Midway Gas Company - L. A. 1912s. H. M. Daugherty, supt.
  - Miles, H. E. - Wn., D. C. 1913v.p. Chief Commerce of U. S., chrmn. Com. on Coms.
  - Miller, John B. - L. A. 1911pres. So. Cal. Edison Co.
  - Milliron, Clark J. - L. A. 1921atty, (1)
  - Mills, James Riverside 1908, 11, 12supt. Arlington Hts. Fruit Co.
  - Millsiaugh, Jesse F. - L. A. 1911pres. State Normal School
  - ?Mitchell, E. F. - Sacramento 1910? Calif. Exec. Off.
  - Mosbacher, George L.A. 1919pres. Fed of Jewish Charities of L.A.
  - Modoc Co. Republican Cent. Com. - Alturas 1912s. J.T.Negley, sec. s. E.C. Bonner, chrmn.
  - Mono Co. [Repub. Cent. Com.] (Roosevelt or Progressive). Bridgeport 1912s George Delury, Co clerk
  - Monroe, Charles - L.A. 1910, 14, 15Judge Superior Ct
  - Monterey Co. [Repub. Cent.] Com. - Salinas. 1912T.P. Joy, Co. Clerk
  - Moore, E.C. - L.A. 1907, 11, 12Supt. L.A. City Schs. head, Dept. of Educ., Yale University
  - Morgan, George F.C. - S.F. 1912M.D., minister etc.
  - Morris, Isadot - L.A. 1910, 15atty
  - Morrison, M.D. - Halifax, Nova Scotia 1918dif. med. offt. Nova Scotia Workmens Compensation Bd.
  - Morrison, Willis I. - L.A. 1910-13, 1918atty; L.A. County Repub. Centl. Com., Industrial Acc. Bd., judge Superior Repub. St. Cent. Com.
  - Mosbachel, George - L.A. 1919Pres. Fed. of Jewish Charities
  - Moseley, Alfred - Del Monte 1912Coronado
  - Moss, Leon F. - L.A. 1919atty
  - Mott, Frank K. - Oaklaud 1907, 08, 11, 12Mayor
  - Moulton, D A. - Sacramento 1911deputy controller
  - Mouser, Frank H. - Sacramento 1913, 15, 17Calif Assb.
  - Moyer, Allen - S.F. 1917-20real estate
  - Mueller, Oscar C. - L.A. 1908, 17, 18atty Pres L.A. Chamber of Commerce
  - Mulholland, William - L.A. 1911, 12, 13chf. eng. L.A. Bur. of Water Water Works and Supply
  - Mundell, M. - L.A. 1912re: Jewish vote position at Whittier
  - Munroe, W. B. - Cambridge, Mass. 1915, 16, 19Harvard, Dept. of Govt. Woodruff Testimonial Com. - Nat'l Municipal Lg.
  - Murdock, Victor - Wn., D.C. 1915, 16U.S. Hse of Reps. Cem. Ways & Means Pregressive Nat'l Com.
  - Murphy, [W.?] - Pasadena 1915, 16
  - Mutual Life Ins. of N.Y. - L.A. 1911, 13s. H.E.Maxson, Mgr.
  - Mushet, W.C. - L.A. 1909candidate for Mayor
  - Myers, John S. - L.A. 1913, 15, 21City Auditer
  - Municipal Conference of 1913 - L.A. Apr.-Jun., 1913 - n.d.st. Vincent G.Gelcich, asst. sec.; Meyer Lissner, chrmn., Campaign Com; t. Dell A. Schweitzer, sec.; s. F.W. Braun, treas.; s. Stoddard Jess, chrmn.; Charles G. Andrews, chrmn. fin. com.; s. C. Ziegler; & Louis W. Myers, chrmn. exec. Com. s. W.N. Snowden
  - Municipal League of L.A. - 1909-14, 16-19 n.d.s. J.O. Koepfli pres., C.D. Willard, sec.; st. R.W. Burnham J.A. Anderson, L. Lichtenberger, fin. com.; Edwin O. Eitgertain, sec.; s. H.S. Ryerson, asst. sec.; t. Elbert Wing, pre s. Seward C. Simons, sec.; & minutes Dec 1916, 17 Jans. Charles H. Langmuir, pres.; Anthony Pratt, sec.
  - *Myers, Louis W. - L.A. 1912, 13, 16-18, 20, 21atty. Judge Super. chairman. exec. com. Mun. Conf. 1913
  - Mun. Lg. of L.A. - s. R.E. Crandall, acting see.
  - Naftzger, A. H. - L. A. 1912, 16, 17, 20, 21chrmn. St. Coun. of Defense for Calif exec. com. & vice-chairman, Indus. Acc. Cmm.
  - Nagle, Francis G. - 1913
  - * Napapht Co. Repub Cent. Com (& Progressive Comm) - Napa 1912s, Perey S. King
  - Napthaly, S. L. - Wm., D.C. 1921
  - Nash, Joseph H. - Redwood City 1916San Matee Co. Clk.
  - Nat'l Adjusting Assoc. - L.A. 1913st. H. Ross Douglass, mgr.
  - Nat'l City Planning Conf. (Boston) 12 1914, 15, 17s. Flarel Shurtleff, sec.
  - Nat'l Civil Serv. Reform League - N.Y. 1911s. Elliot H. Goodwin, see
  - Nat'l Economic League - Boston 1913, 16, 18, 21s. J.W. Beastson, sec
  - Nat'l Geographic Soc. - Wn, D.C. 1912s.G.P. Austin, sec.
  - Nat'l. Jewish Consumptive ReliefAssoc. of So. Cal. - L. A. 1913s. Dr. H.M. Silverberg, ticket chrmn
  - Nat'l Municipal Review - Phila. N.Y. 1914, 15, 20 *s. Clinton Rogers Woodruff ed. pub. by Natl Muni Lg.; s*. Richard S. Chilols editor
  - Nat'l Progressive Repub. LG. - Wn., D.C. 1911s. Frederic C. Howe, sec.
  - Nat'l Repub. Alliance - N. Y. 1911s. George A. Melbourne, pres.
  - Nat'l Roosevelt Com. - Wn., D.C. 1912s. G.R. Manchester
  - Nat'l Short Ballot Org. - N.Y. 1915, 16, 18s. H.S. Gilbertson, exec
  - Nat'l. Tax Assoc. - Columbus, Ohio 1908s. Allen Ripley Foote, pres.
  - Nat'l. Young Hens Taft Cl. - Chicago 1912s. Harry Swam, sec.
  - Nauhann, Aug. - L.A. 1916, 17
  - Nat'l Municipal LG, - Philadelphia 1908, 10-12, 14-19, 21H.W. Dodds, sec * Clinton Regers Woodruff see. List. Calif. members s. Charles J. Bonaparte chrmn; s. E. D. Chappell William Dudley Foulke, pres. Geo. Burnham, Jr. treas.
  - Negley/ James T. - Alturas, Calif. 1910, 12, 13see Modoc Co. Repub. Cent. Comm postmaster Alturas
  - Nelson, Howard Franklin - Gardena, Cal. 1916 author, inventor, etc.
  - Neumiller, C.L. - Stockton 1911, 12, 20atty Neumiller & Ditz
  - Neumiller & Ditz - Stockton 1920s. David B. Lyman C. L. Neumiller
  - Nevada Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - Grass Valley 1912s, E. H. Armstrong pres. Grass Valley Repub. Club
  - Newby, Nathan - L.A. 1911, 13atty, chairman. Civic Righteousness Com, Church Federation of L.A.
  - New Jersey State Dept. - Trenton, N.j. 1912s. [Ths. F. Main ?]
  - Newman, Harry C. - L.A. 1911 & n.d.(& Madeline) dentist
  - Newman, Lester I. - S.F. 1919med. dir. State Compensation Ins. Fund.
  - Nelles, Fred C. - L.A. 1911-13,15-20The Nelles Co. treas., Good Govt. Org; pres & mgr Gas Power Machinery Co. supt. Whittier State School
  - Newmark, Henry M. - L.A. 1911, 12
  - Newmark, M.A.- L.A. 1909, 11, 13, 15importer
  - Newmark, M.A. & Co. - L.A. 1911, 15
  - Newmire, Earl - L.A. 1912partner of Isader Morris
  - Newspaper Enterprise Assoc. - Wm. D.C. 1911s, Gilson Garden Wn. correspondence
  - New Republic - N.Y. 1918s. Berkeley G. Tohey, circ. mgr.
  - Ng Poon Chew - S. F. 1912Reg. ed, Chung Sai Yat Po
  - Neylan, John Francis - Sacramento 1912, 13,14,15chrmn., Calif. State Board of Control, S.F. atty. publisher S. F. Call
  - Nielsen, Neil - S.F. 1915Trade Cmmr. to Am. for N.S.W. Australia
  - Nolan, George N. - L.A. 1908, 21see L.A. Charter Revision Cmm.
  - Non Partisan City Cent. Com. - L.A. 1906ptd. James A. Foshay chairman
  - Non Partisan Org. of So. Calif. - L.A. 1915 & n.d.s. Charles S. Crail, sec.
  - North American Civic LG for Immigrants - N.Y. 1914s. Frances A. Relles my.
  - Nourse, J. R. - L.A. 1916, Washington, D.C. 1920L.A. Examiner, Universal Service, Inc. Washington Bureau
  - Nye, A.B. - Sacramento 1907, 10, 11Calif Controller
  - Oakland, Cal., 1st Hebrew Congr. of - Oakland 1921t. Frederick Kahn, chrmn. cemetery com.; t. M. Wahrhartig, sec.
  - O'Brien, Florence J. - 1915,Chico 1919Panama - Pacific International Exposition Cmm. of Cal. ed., Chico Enterprise
  - O'Brien, Frederick - Riverside 1912for Riverside Enterprise
  - O'Brien, P.P. - L.A. 1921pres. L.A. Board of Public Works
  - Odgers, Harriet B. - Sacramento 1912, 13, 15, 16Calif. exec. off.
  - Off, Edward T. - Mojave 1913,S.F. 1917, 1918, 1919Cal. St. Bd. of Pharmacy res. mgr. Fairment Hotel
  - Ogden, T.A. - Redlands, 1916, 1917, [1918?], 1919, 1921asst cashier Union Savings Bank
  - Ohio Constitutional Conv. - Columbus, O. 1912s. C.B. Galbreath sec.
  - Ohio Industrial Cmm. - Columbus, O. 1916st. Emile E. Watson actuary
  - Oil Industry Assoc. - S.F. 1915
  - Older, Fremont - S.F. 1911, 12, 13, 17The Bulletin 7 & 1 tel.
  - Oliver, James M. - S.F. 1914, 19, 20atty
  - Olmstead, Frederick Law L.A. 1911, 12Brookline, Mass. landscape architect
  - Olney, Warren, Jr. - S.F. 1920cand. for assoc. justice Calif. Supreme Ct.
  - Oneil, Phila L. - L.A. 1913, 14Chamber of Commerce
  - O'Neill, Edward - L.A. 1917Clune's Broadway Theatre
  - Orange Co Repub. Cent. Com. - Santo Ana 1912s. A. J. Jackman, chrmn.
  - Ormsey, A.S. - Martinez 1912Contra Costa Co. dep. D.A.
  - Orpheum Theatre & Realty Co., Inc. - S.F. 1919, 20s. M. Meyerfeld, Jr.
  - Osborne, H.Z. - L.A. 1911-13, 15-17, 19Ch of C. - chrmn. G.A.R. Co. exec. dir. G.A.R. 46th Nat'l Encampment, G.A.R. St. r. cmdr-in-chief L.A. Bd. of Pub. Works, U.S. Rep. for Calif.
  - Oster, Charles - Paris, France 1911, 12author? on L-R Lg?
  - Otis, Frank - S.F. 1917atty
  - Otis Elevator Co. - L.A. 1915s. W.G.[Kennary], Keanan Dare Lever, supt.; [Helbren,] Local service agt.; J.D. Heyt, acct; C. Leatham, service agt.; W. Lewis, G.S. Gilbert
  - Outlook - N.Y. 1911
  - Outlook Assoc - L.A. 1915s. Mrs. James F. Scherfee, pres.; Mrs. David Chambers McCan, chrmn.
  - Outlook Co. - N.Y. 1915
  - Overell, J. M., Furniture Co. - L.A. 1912s. A.G.Overell, v.p. & mgr.
  - Owen, E.H. - L.A. 1911clerk, U.S. Dist. Court
  - Owen, F.V. - L.A. 1912see Good Govt Org
  - Owen, Frank H. - Colton 1910[Repub.] St. Committeeman ed., Colton Chronicle
  - Owens, Madison T. - Whittier 1910, 12atty
  - Owl Drug Co. - L.A. 1915, 17s. A.R. Speckt, So. Cal. District mgr.; s. W. M. Berg, sec.; G. F. Pfaffenberger, op. mgr.
  - Oyama, Ujiro - L.A. 1919Japanese consul
  - Pacific Electric Railway Co. - L.A. 1908s J McMillan, traffic mgr.
  - Pacific Municipalities - S.F. 1911s. mg. ed. W.J. Locke, offl. publ. of League of Calif Municipalities
  - Pacific Mutual Life Insurance Co. of Cal. - L.A. 1916s. D. M. Berkeley, cahsier; s. George I. Cochran, pres.
  - Page, Benjamin E. - L.A N.Y. 1911, 13atty
  - Palestine Relief Com. - L.A. 1915s. M.R. Newmark, chrmn.; s. Harry A. Goldman, sec.
  - Panama - Pacific Internat'l Exposition - S.F. 1911,s. James Rolph, Jr. acting pres., Rudolph Taussig, sec.
  - Pardee, George C. - Oakland 1911, 12, 1 ltr, 3 tels.
  - Parsons, Edwin T. - Stockton 1915, 16
  - Pasadena, Nat'l Bank Of - pasadena 1915, 16, 17s. J.B. Coulton pres. s. Leen V. Shaw, cashier, Herbert C. Holt, asst. cashier
  - Pasadena City Assessor - Pasadena 1916s. C.S. Nelson, dep.
  - Pathe Exchange, Inc. - L.A. 1915s. [B.E. Lopen]
  - Pathe Freres - Jersey City, N.J. 1915s. Eric E. Mayell, Pathe News
  - Patton, George S. - L.A. 1915
  - Payne, George Henry - N.Y. 1912Roosevelt Com.
  - Peard, Frank F. - Buffalo, N.Y. 1916, 19
  - Pearson, B.F. - L.A. 1911, 13trustee, Whittier State School
  - Peck, Elbert E. - L.A. 1912, 15, 16, 17atty, chairman. Peoples Campaign Com
  - Pendleton, Elliott Hunt - Cincinnati, Ohio 1908
  - Pennsylvania St. Railroad Commission - Harrisburg, Penn. 1912s. Archibald B. Millar, sec.
  - Perkins, George C. - Wn. D.C. 1911u.s. Senator
  - Peoples Campaign Com. - L.A. 1913s. E.E. Leighton chrmn. compaign com
  - Peoples Charter Conf - L.A. 1912s. Edward E. Leighton, sec.
  - Peoples Lobby - Wn., D.C. 1907s. & of Henry Beach Needhaus, see.
  - Peoples Power Bond Com. - L.A. 1914, 17st. & ptd. L.H. Valentine. chrmn.; st. M. Lissner, chrmn., Election Day Com, st Walter R. Stevenson exec. sec.; st. V.G. Geleich, org. mgr.
  - Pepperdine, George - San Diego, 1916
  - Perkins, Dorothy - N.Y. n.d. Dec. 8
  - Perry, Everett R. - L.A. 1912, 15, 17librarian, L.A. Public Library; ? clerk Library Bd., see. Library Bd.
  - Perkins, George W. - L.A. N.Y. 1911-13, 14-18Progressive Party chrmn. exec. com. Progressive Nat'l Com.
  - Petterson, A.S. - Santa Barbara 1908, 15, n.d.editor Independen
  - Pew, Marlen E. - N.Y. 1915genl. mgr. Gotham Book Society
  - Peyton, David C. - Jeffersonville, Ind. 1915genl supt. Indiana Reformate
  - Phelan, James D. - S.F. 1905,?10, 11, 14, 15-17, 19U.S. Senate
  - Philadelphia, Pa. City Parks Assoc - Phila, 1914s. Andrew Wright Crawford, s
  - Phillips, [J.] - N.Y. 1913American Magazine
  - Phillips, Ida J. - Van Nuys, 1920
  - Pillsbury, Arthur J. - S.F. 1901, 11, 12treas. & mgr. Calif. Weekly Industrial Accident Cmm, (Calif.)
  - Pinchot, Amos R.E. - N.Y. 1912, 14atty.
  - Placer Co. Repub. Cent. Com, - Auburn 1912s. _____ Lowell, Co. clerk
  - Plehn Carl C. - Berkeley 1907, 08sec. Calif. St. Commission on Revenue & Taxation
  - Plumas Co. Repub. Cent. - Com. - [Quincy, 1912][ H.P. McBeth, Co. clerk]
  - Pinchot, Gifford - Wm D.C. 1912, 16-20Forester. U. S Forest Service (Harry L. Hill = sec.)
  - Poindexter, Miles - Up. 1915, 19U.S. Senate chrmn. Com. on expend. in War Dept., chrmn., Com. on Indian Depreciations
  - Political Equality Lg. - L.A. 1910 - h.d.s. Bess Munn, see S. Grace C. (Mrs. Seward A.) Sciences, pres
  - Pond, Allen B. - Chicago 1915, 20architect
  - Pope, Bertha Mrs. A.U. Stephens for Gov.
  - Porter, Florence Collins - So. Pasadena [1913, 14], 15, 14, 16chrmn. Com. mtg., So. Calif. Bldg. Panama-California Exposition; Johnson for Senator
  - Porter, Melvin P. - Buffalo, N.Y. 1914sec. treas. Municipal Lg. of Buffalo
  - Portugese Republican Club, - Sacramento 1910s. John B. Martin pres
  - Postal Telegraph-Cable Co. L.A., SF. 1907, 17, 20G. W. Hoet, mgr. F.S. Fell, mgr. L.A., H.C. Shaw, supt. 1st dist. Pacific Div.
  - Power, Harold T. - East Auburn, Cal. 1910-12Placer Co. Repub.
  - Powers, L.M. - L.A. 1911M.D. L.A. Health, Dept. Health Commt.
  - Pope, Arthur Upham - Berkeley 1914Prof. U. of C. dept of Philosophy American Neutral Conference Committee, exec. sec. pro-tem
  - Pridham, R.W. - L.A. 1912, 13L.A. Co. Supervisor, chrmn. Bd. of Supervisors
  - Progress - N.Y. 1912s. George Howe, editor
  - Progress - Club - L.A. 1908s. Victor E. Hecht,, Sec.
  - Progressive Co. Cent. Com. - L.A. Co. - L.A. 1915, 1916, & n.d.s. S.C. Graham, chrmn.; s. Mary E. Smith, acting Sec.
  - Progressive National Com. - N.Y. 1912, 18s. E.H. Hooker natl. treas. w/ Mary Garland reply H.E. Hides Com of mfrs. s. Roy C. Durstine, press bureau - H.F.W. ? Progressive Bulletin s. Frances A. Kellor, chief of Service
  - Progressive Nat'l Service - N.Y. 1913s. Edith L.M. Tate, sec. dept. of Service Org.
  - Progressive Nat'l Conv. Com. - Chicago, 1916s. F.P. Corrick, s. George F. Porter, chrmn.
  - Progressive State Cent. Com. - Calif, - S.F. 1915, 16s. Charles R. Detrick, see, s. Percy V. Long, chrmn.
  - Provident Mutual Bldg Loan Assn. - L.A 1909, 11, 13s. J. H. Hunter, sec., v-p
  - Prudential Ins Co. of Am. - L.A. 1911, 19, 20, 22s. H.B. Nelles mgr. So. Cal
  - Public School Committe of One Hunderd - L.A. 1915s. Fred E. Golding, sec.
  - Public Service Regulation - Chicago 1912s. F.H. Reed
  - Putnam, Osgood - S.F. 1912atty
  - Radcliff, George G. (tel) - Sacramento 1911 mem. Repub. St. Exee. Comi.
  - * Randall, Charles H. - Highland Park Calif. 1907, 11publisher Highland Park Herald, Calif. Assb.
  - Recorder Ptg. & Publg. Co. - S.F. 1919, 20
  - Recorder Publg. Co. - Olympia, Wn. 1911
  - Red Cross - L.A. 1919st. Bea Lawler (Mrs. Oscar), chrmn. mail sale xmas seals
  - Redlands Daily Review - Redlands 1905s. W.E.Grigsby bus. mgr.
  - Red-Light Abatement Act - S.F. 1914Mr. Calif. Campaign Com. for s. Franklin Hichborn, cor. sec.
  - Reed, Charles Wesley - S.F. 1915cmmr. & pres. State Civil Service Cmm.
  - Reed, Franklin H. - Chicago 1911ed. Telephony (Am. Telephone Sournal)
  - [Reed, Thomas H.] - San Jose 1918City Mgr. s. by see
  - Reese, David J. - Ventura 1908, 16-19, 21ed. & prop. Ventura Free Press cmmr. & pres. State Civil Service Com.
  - Regensburg, Oscar H. Hollywood 1911see Nat'l Assoc. of the Deaf
  - * Reid, Whitelaw - Millbrae, Cal. 1908 -N.Y. Tribune min. to France, etc., (1)
  - Reily, Schn A. - Patton, Cal. - 1916, 17meel. supt. So. Cal. St. Hospita
  - Remington Typewriter Co. - L.A. 1903, 04
  - Rensberger, E.C. - L.A. 1912bus. mgr. California Outlook
  - - Reppy, Roy V. - L.A. 1919genl. counsel So. Calif. Edison Co.
  - Republican Nat'l Com. - N.Y. 1912, 16, 20James R. Reynolds sec, s. William R. Wilcox, chairman.; Raymond Benjamin, asst. to chairman.